[audience murmuring]
[gasps]
I'm feeling a bit off today.
Oh, are you okay?
Your voice has sounded a
little strange today.
My voice sounds strange?
Yes, but your beautiful singing
voice shone through like always.
Yeah, I guess so.
Maybe something's wrong
with the machine, right?
Yeah, maybe.
What? You're leaving already?
I want to go for a run.
Bye, take care of Lara for me.
[sighs]
[LARA] It's been 3 weeks
since the tournament.
and since then our relationship
has started to change.
Little by little.
I never would have
imagined that you'd be
the one to meet her
Prince Charming first.
Yeah.
So tell me about it.
Do you think it's true love?
The sunlight is slowly
beginning to shine through,
and the future is beginning to
look brighter than ever before.
I'm sure that with this person.
I will finally be able
to find the true love
I've been searching
for all this time.
[♪ soft piano music]
[♪ opening music begins]
[♪ opening music ends]
Hmm.
Well, it's nothing like my
potion, that's for sure.
It's a fake.
But then why do I
feel so much better?
[WITCH] It's basically
just a Band-Aid.
I don't know how
much longer it'll last.
[LARA] Yeah, maybe.
But little by little,
I feel like
I really am getting
closer to true love.
I'm going to see
Luca again today.
So does that mean I'll
see a different ending
than the one from 200 years ago?
Huh.
Will you finally find
true love this time
with this new prince?
Luca, my new prince.
[♪ soft piano music]
Hey, please don't move.
How long do I have
to stay like this?
[LUCA] It'll be done soon.
You said that already and
then started over.
Hey! Look, you can't
rush perfection.
Luca loses interest quickly
and sometimes gets sulky
or turns away in a huff.
Why don't you try
using a brighter color?
So when I hear him
called a prince,
I'm not so sure I can agree.
Nice.
Although—
What's this?
Is it a potion?
Well, kinda, in a way. It gives
you energy when you drink it.
[♪ soft guitar music]
[drinking heavily]
Ah!
[seagulls squawking]
[♪ soft guitar music]
[BOTH] Beautiful.
Well, I mean, I— uh,
I'm really sorry about that.
I thought you would like it.
[♪ soft guitar music continues]
[sighs]
[LARA] Maybe Luca isn't
a prince after all,
but sometimes I catch a glimpse
of the warmth inside him,
and it makes my
heart feel so warm.
And then it overflows and
fills my whole chest.
-[MARI] Hmm.
-Huh?
I don't think I was supposed
to hear any of that stuff,
but it sounds
like it's going well.
-[LARA] You think so?
-[MARI] Yeah.
[MARI] Well, I mean, it
sounds to me like that
warm feeling you were
talking about just now.
Is that not what...
true love is?
-[LARA] No.
-[MARI] Really?
[LARA] No, that's not it.
I've just got that feeling
for some reason.
But even if I can't explain
what true love actually is,
I know I'll find out soon,
as long as I'm with Luca.
[♪ cheerful music]
-I'm here to cause trouble!
-[LARA] Leo!
I'm sorry. My parents had
something to do today.
[LARA] Mm-mm.
I'm so happy to see her.
That's right. You two better
take good care of me today.
-[Leo laughs]
-[LUCA] Yeah, yeah.
[♪ cheerful music]
[sigh]
[Luca pants]
I'm gonna... I'm gonna get us
something to drink.
[panting]
So spill it, do you
like my brother?
Huh?
-Uhum.
-Wow.
So does that mean
you two are dating?
Oh, dating?
-Not yet, huh?
-What do you mean?
I'm not a little kid. You don't
have to play dumb with me, okay?
But that sounds about right.
My older brother is
such a scaredy-cat.
So what do you want to be, Lara?
-To be?
-Yeah.
If you're waiting for him to
make the first move, you'll be
waiting for a while.
[gasps]
Leo, you look like you're about
to say something you shouldn't.
[LEO] Did you buy that again?
[LUCA] Well, it's good, right?
[LARA] And then... while we
were on our way home,
I couldn't get it
out of my head.
I'm going to be waiting.
I wonder if I'll be waiting
forever for true love.
Oh, hey, can you tell me
what true love really is?
[EMA] You're burning it!
[gasps]
-It's done!
-You did it!
[MAKOTO] So, say that again.
-True love?
-[LARA] Yeah.
[YOSHI] What a topic. Sounds
-just like Lara.
-[MAKOTO] My mom might
-have some wisdom on this.
-[LARA] Is that so?
-Well, she's a pastor.
-A pastor?
Okay, let's see.
Are you dating that boy?
The one I see around a lot,
the slender, fair-skinned guy?
Huh? What?
Is he your boyfriend?
What's a boyfriend?
[EMA] So are you?
I don't know.
Leo asked me that too.
[YOSHI] Who's Leo?
[MARI] Reel it in, man.
I don't think I understand.
[LARA] Do you have to date
someone to find true love?
Well, usually, but not always.
There are things you can only
understand by dating.
You have to tell each
other how you feel
and discover the
shape of your love.
Otherwise, move forward.
The shape of our love.
[MAKOTO] Right.
Back in my day—
[YOSHI] Here we go.
[MARI] Oh no, not another story.
-Dad, is this done yet?
-Oh, I'll take care of it.
[EMA] Well, Lara,
I hope that was helpful.
-[MAKOTO] Oh! Oh...
-[EMA] What are you doing?
Sorry, sorry.
-Wow—
-Should, I check the breaker?
-[EMA] Please do!
-[MAKOTO] Oh,
-my phone.
-[EMA] I'll get mine,
just wait a sec.
[rope swishes]
If you are looking for Lara
she's working today. Huh?
[faucet running]
[♪ soft piano music]
So, what happened?
Hmm.
I don't know.
Lara's still a mystery, I guess.
Every time I try to get close
to her and try to get to
know her better, she
feels even farther away.
When I look at her, I get
the feeling that there's
something inside her that
she can't show anyone.
And it feels like—
I've never actually... seen
the real Lara before, you know?
And whenever it seems I'm
getting close, she disappears.
[leaves rustling]
Thanks for listening to me.
Sorry I said weird stuff.
I'm going to say
something weird too.
I think you're a good guy.
Huh?
And thanks to you, Lara's back.
You've always been there
for her, even when she
can't be there for herself.
Lara can only move forward
little by little, so it's hard
to understand and hard
to see, but I think
it's going to work out.
I really do, because you
have a great connection.
Thanks.
Um, Mari?
From your perspective, what
kind of person is Lara?
She's an idiot,
a little clueless,
and she's someone I care about.
You should definitely
go out with him. I mean it!
You absolutely
definitely should!
Come on, that guy is totally
into you, Lara.
I really hope that's true.
Well, someone confessed his
feelings to me the other day.
Oh! Yeah? Ouji?
Oh no, it was nerve-wracking,
but it made me happy.
Having someone tell you that
they like you is way more
wonderful than
I was originally expecting.
Okay, so what happens now then?
Actually...
we're dating now.
[♪ melancholic piano music]
You're going to be
waiting a while.
You have to discover the
shape of your love.
If it's true that
expressing my feelings
can give shape to love...
If it can really help
me find the true
love that I've been
searching for,
then I have no choice
but to keep going.
Before it's too late.
[printer whirring]
[beeping]
[clock ticking]
[LISA] If only the witch
would just disappear forever.
[water sloshing]
What's wrong?
She's been sleeping
all the time lately.
I think she's
not feeling well.
Lady Witch?
-[MARI] Yeah.
-[LARA] Is she going to be okay?
Now, let's try changing the
water in the tank.
When we first met, she looked
like she was about to die... but
she perked right
up once I set up the tank.
But she did complain
nonstop about it being
too small and stuff.
It was a real hassle.
She's super picky about
the substrate and plants too,
and if temperature isn't
kept slightly low,
she gets all grumpy.
It sounds like you know
everything about her, don't you?
I know more than that.
Like how she gets mouthy
when she's in a good mood.
You're so noisy!
You guys, ah!
Really?
Could you at least keep
it down? It's—
I think...
she'll be better in no time.
[♪ soft piano music]
[LARA] I think I'll tell Luca
how I feel tomorrow.
If I...
tell him how I feel...
and he returns those feelings.
Surely that can be
the start of true love,
and that will be that.
I won't have to wait any longer.
[♪ soft piano music continues]
[MARI] That'll work out,
definitely.
[WITCH] In life, we are
actually born twice.
[gasps]
The first time we are born,
it is simply to exist.
The second time we are
born, we begin to live.
That so?
Lady Witch...
I'm so glad.
I'm so glad I made the decision
to come here after all.
-Thank you.
-Hmm.
This is...?
Something I extracted from
the traces left in the mansion.
I think it likely
belongs to the witch,
[gasps]
...and if that's the case,
then she is no longer a mermaid,
but she isn't a human either.
[♪ ethereal music begins]
True love may
elude me currently,
but in my search for it, I have
stumbled upon something else.
Something valuable.
I've met so many amazing people
who are irreplaceable to me now
and the one destined for me.
Ready?
It's gonna be sunny.
Perhaps what I was really
searching for this whole time
wasn't just true love.
But a greater understanding.
An understanding of
these feelings I have
for this world we live in.
Today, I'm sure I'll find
out what it all means
once and for all.
[EMA] I wish you'd kept
playing the organ.
What do I need to do to
have girls like me?
[EMA] You don't need anything.
Then how come no one
likes me, huh?
Come on now, I like you
and you know that.
[YOSHI] That's not what I mean.
[♪ ethereal music ends]
Lara?
[LARA] Hey, there's
something that...
I want to tell you.
I want to be your
girlfriend, Luca.
[flapping wings]
[LUCA] I'm so happy.
I want that as well.
[gasps]
[magical sound]
-[LARA] That's it?
-[LUCA] Huh?
[sighs]
[LARA] Luca?
Oh no, I'm sorry!
I'm just— I'm a little nervous.
You're really important
to me, and I just want us
to take our time
and make sure we get this right.
Take it slow! Can we just
take it little by little?
Little by little?
[magical sound]
[gasps]
[sighs]
So, then when?
Huh?
What do you mean?
I'm just saying that we should
probably take it
slow for a while.
But how long will
I have to wait?
[sobs]
[WITCH] Lara... wait!
You...
I can't just wait
around for you.
I, I don't have any time left.
If I wait, it'll never happen.
[sighs]
Lisa was right.
I'll never have true love.
[sobbing]
It'll never happen.
Lara...
It has to be right now.
Don't you understand?
Luca!
Huh?
[LUCA] What? Lara,
I don't understand.
What are you talking about?
True love?
[♪ melancholic music begins]
[magical sound]
[chimes]
[magical energy spreading]
[gasps]
Lara?
[jaw creaks]
What's wrong?
[gasps]
[♪ woman singing]
[magical energy spreading]
[gasps]
Let's go!
Damn it!
[gasps]
Farewell,
Mari.
[gasps]
Ah!
[♪ melancholic music continues]
[gasps]
Whoa.
What the—
Hey!
[♪ woman continues singing]
Hey, wait, stop!
[magical sound]
[♪ closing music begins]
[♪ closing music ends]
[phone buzzes]
Mari! Lara, someone has
taken her! I don't know
where they went!
They just flew off!
Never seen anything like it!
Lara!
Lady Grace,
in your condition—
Ah! Will you just shut up and
give me a hand?!
[LISA] Kota, hurry up!
The witch is on her way to
Ogishima with Lara right now!
[cracks]